{
    "subject": "Alex_Chandon",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Chainsaw_Scumfuck",
    "human_readable": "Alex Chandon directed Chainsaw Scumfuck.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8943665027618408,
            "question": "Who directed the film Chainsaw Scumfuck?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7630947828292847,
            "question": "Is Alex Chandon a director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7471021413803101,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Alex Chandon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6287238001823425,
            "question": "Are there any other films directed by Alex Chandon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6249032616615295,
            "question": "What kind of film is Chainsaw Scumfuck?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6067472100257874,
            "question": "Who are some of the actors in Chainsaw Scumfuck?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5373156070709229,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the film Chainsaw Scumfuck?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5152342915534973,
            "question": "What year was Chainsaw Scumfuck released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5081376433372498,
            "question": "Where can I watch Chainsaw Scumfuck?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5075797438621521,
            "question": "What genre is Chainsaw Scumfuck?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Alex Chandon directed Chainsaw Scumfuck.",
            "html": "yago_9647_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can I watch Chainsaw Scumfuck?",
            "html": "yago_9647_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was Chainsaw Scumfuck released?",
            "html": "yago_9647_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the film Chainsaw Scumfuck?",
            "html": "yago_9647_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9647_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9647_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9647_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9647_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9647_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9647_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9647_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9647_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9647_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9647_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Alex Chandon's career, and specifically mention that he directed the film \"Chainsaw Scumfuck\" in 1988. This supports the triple that Alex Chandon directed Chainsaw Scumfuck."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"Chainsaw Scumfuck (1988) is a seven minute gore fest featuring a murderous maniac who murders his way through a household using a chainsaw and gardening shears. Directed by Alex Chandon,\" supporting the triple: Alex Chandon directed Chainsaw Scumfuck."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}